https://www.cubsucc.com/privacy/

This website uses cookies.
About Us
Why Cork University Business School?
About Us
Why Cork University Business School?
Privacy Statement
This statement relates to the privacy practices of University College Cork – National University of Ireland, Cork (“the University”) in connection with the University’s websites.
General statement
The University fully respects your right to privacy and actively seeks to preserve the privacy rights of those who share personal information with the University.
Collection and use of personal information
The University does not collect any personal information about you on these websites apart from information which you volunteer (for example by using our online feedback form). Any personal information which you volunteer to the University in connection with these websites will be treated in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1988 and Data Protection (Amendment) Act 2003. Accordingly, the University shall only process such information in line with the purpose for which you provided it to the extent necessary to provide you with the information or service you require.  The University shall not disclose your information to third parties unless you are specifically informed otherwise or we require a third party to process the information on our behalf (in which case the University requires these third parties to comply with its instructions and we require that they do not use your personal information for their own business purposes, unless you have explicitly consented to the use of your personal information in this way).
Links
The University is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. The privacy practices on these websites may differ from that on the University’s websites, and we advise that you review the other websites’ policies before providing personal information.
Within the University domain (.ucc.ie) you may find websites over which the University has no editorial responsibility. Such sites can include the websites of student organisations, etc. While the University expects compliance with this privacy statement at such sites, please contact the Digital Estate Working Group if you encounter University websites that are not compliant with this privacy statement.
Right of Access and Rectification
You have the right to ask for a copy of your personal data (in which case the University is entitled to charge a nominal fee). If you wish to avail of this right, you should submit a written request to:
Information Compliance Officer
University College Cork
Western Road
Cork
Phone: (0)21 490 3949
Email: foi@ucc.ie
In order to protect your privacy, you may also be asked to provide suitable proof of identification. If any of your details are incorrect please let us know and we will amend them.
Revisions to Privacy Statement
The University may revise this privacy statement from time to time. Changes to this privacy statement will be posted here so you should periodically check this page to review the most recent statement. If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of the University’s websites should be referred to the Information Compliance Officer at the address set out above.
Last updated: February 2016
